Finding Aid for Richard C. Frank papers, 1958-2004
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Visual Material
  The Visual Material series consists of files that contain visual material related to the projects listed under the Project Files series. The separation between the project files and the visual materials has been maintained from its original arrangement. The series contains two subseries: Slides and Negatives/Photographs. The Slides subseries is arranged according to its original, alphabetical order. The project slides document floor plans, building exteriors and interiors, and construction progress. The Negatives/Photographs subseries has been arranged alphabetically, under a project name. It is important to note that projects represented in the Negative/Photographs subseries may also contain negatives and photographs in the corresponding Project Files series.
  - Slides
    - Ann Arbor Details (Box 39)
    - Slide Presentation Record (Box 39)
    - Adrian Library (Box 39)
    - Ann Arbor
      - Fire Station (Box 39)
      - Historic Views (Box 39)
      - Westside Neighborhood (Box 39)
      - Westside Neighborhood, Tree Planting (Box 39)
      - Trolley (Box 39)
    - Arnold Transit, Co. (Box 39)
    - Bagley Avenue (Box 39)
    - Battle Creek Railway Station (Box 39)
    - Battle Creek San. (Box 39)
    - Bay City (Box 39)
    - Benton Harbor (Box 39)
    - Bidwell Building (Box 39)
    - Bishop and Shelton (Box 39)
    - Boyne City (Box 39)
    - Calumet (Box 40)
    - Calumet-Harmonie (Box 40)
    - Chelsea Railroad Station (Box 40)
    - Chittenden Hall-MSU (Box 40)
    - Corktown (Box 40)
    - Crossroads Village
      - Proposed (Box 40)
      - Master Plan (Box 40)
      - Atlas Grist Mill (Box 40)
      - Barn (Box 40)
      - Dr. Baubour Office (Box 40)
      - Blacksmith Shop (Box 40)
      - Buzzel House (Box 40)
      - Carriage Barn (Box 40)
      - Commercial Building (Box 40)
      - Village Church (Box 40)
      - Cider Mill (Box 40)
      - Clayton Townhall (Box 40)
      - Corrunna Road School (Box 40)
      - Davison Depot (Box 40)
      - Durant Barn (Box 40)
      - Fenton Opera House (Box 40)
      - Fox House (Box 40)
      - General (Box 40)
      - Hammer House (Box 40)
      - Hess Sawmill (Box 40)
      - Lawyers Office (Box 40)
      - Millpond (Box 40)
    - Downtown Detroit People Mover (Box 40)
    - Detroit Stove (Box 40)
    - Depot Town (Box 40)
    - Dunham House (Box 40)
    - Durand (Box 40)
    - The Earle (Box 40)
    - EC of Preservation (Box 40)
    - Fair Lane (Box 41)
    - Fenton (Box 41)
    - Flint W.S. (Box 41)
    - Fort Michilimackinac (Box 41)
    - Fort Michilimackinac State Park (Box 41)
    - Fort Wayne (Box 41)
    - Fort Wilkins (Box 41)
    - General Preservation (Box 41)
    - Grand Haven (Box 41)
    - Grand Ledge (Box 41)
    - Grand Rapids (Box 41)
    - Greenfield Village (Box 41)
    - Gun Lake, Michigan (Box 41)
    - I.C.C. Michigan House (Box 41)
    - Ionia (Box 41)
    - Jefferson Avenue Presbyterian Church (Box 41)
    - Kalamazoo Depot (Box 41)
    - Kalamazoo Water Tower (Box 41)
    - Lansing (Box 41)
    - Lansing Women's Club House (Box 41)
    - Library of Congress (Box 41)
    - Lovell-Webber (Box 41)
    - MMM Bus Development Presentation (Box 41)
    - Mackinac Island (Box 41)
    - Manistee (Box 41)
    - Marshall (Box 41)
    - Miscellaneous-Planning (Box 41)
    - Monroe Block (Box 41)
    - Monroe Center (Box 41)
    - Monroe, City of (Box 41)
    - Moross House (Box 41)
    - Michigan Society of Planning Officials Training Workshop, Community Appearance, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Michigan Society of Planning Officials Training Workshop, Community Appearance, 5 folders (Box 42)
    - Navarre-Anderson Trading Post (Box 42)
    - North Lansing Historic District (Box 42)
    - Orchestra Hall (Box 42)
    - P/UD/I Office (Box 42)
    - P/UD/I Office Addition (Box 42)
    - Saline Boundary (Box 42)
    - Schoolcraft House (Box 42)
    - Storefront Design (Box 42)
    - Sibley House (Box 42)
    - Smithsonian (Box 42)
    - Spaulding (Box 42)
    - State Street (Box 42)
    - St. Ignance (Box 42)
    - Ticknor-Cambell House, Cobblestone Farm (Box 42)
    - Torch Lake (Box 42)
    - Turner Dodge House, Lansing (Box 42)
    - Waterloo Farm Museum (Box 42)
    - Williamsburg (Box 42)
    - Wing House] (Box 42)
    - Woodward East (Box 42)
  - Negatives/ Photographs
    - Alpha Phi House, Olivet College negatives (Box 43)
    - Ann Arbor negatives 1976 (Box 43)
    - Ann Arbor Fire Station negatives, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Ann Arbor People negatives (Box 43)
    - Broadway Streetscape (Box 43)
    - Crossroad Village negatives (Box 43)
    - Depot Town negatives (Box 43)
    - Frank Interior photographs (Box 43)
    - Gilbert House negatives (Box 43)
    - Grand Rapids Public Library, West Side Branch negatives (Box 43)
    - Gun Lake Photographs (Box 43)
    - Flint Survey, Water Street District negatives (Box 43)
    - Fort Wilkins negatives (Box 43)
    - Ionia negatives (Box 43)
    - Lake Erie Gateway Study negatives (Box 43)
    - Latino Community Detroit negatives (Box 43)
    - Lovell-Weber negatives (Box 43)
    - Macon negatives (Box 43)
    - Michigan House (project no. 1207) negatives (Box 43)
    - Monroe Center negatives (Box 43)
    - North Lansing negatives (Box 43)
    - Oakland Cemetery negatives (Box 43)
    - Pabst Building, Old Atlas Township Hall (Box 43)
    - P/UD/I-Dick Frank Photographs (Box 43)
    - P/UD/I Project Photographs, 3 folders (Box 43)
    - St. Mary's Church negatives (Box 43)
    - University of Detroit negatives (Box 43)
    - Woodward East Negatives and Photographs, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Ypsilanti C.D. Public Housing negatives (Box 43)